When I was a kid, the first English sentence that I learned was not about daddy or mommy.
The first English sentence I learned was written all over my toys and it was made in China.
All my toys, electronics and school supplies were made in China and the kid in me always
wondered.
Why is this made in China?
Why not somewhere else?
Now that I'm in China, I found the answer.
This country works in ways that I've never ever seen before.
They work hard, they work fast, they work cheap.
There are a billion Chinese people who build everything from skyscrapers to laptops,
to iPhones, to a stupid plastic toys.
To make this in a different country, then that country needs to be better.
Faster and cheaper than here in China.
Yes!
And from what I see, that's a really hard thing to do.
That's one minute!
See you tomorrow!